now you don't the stabilizer what did
you see Minh what what did you do casual
airport drive
[Music]
but we should always have a stabilizer
with us at all times that's right of
course Co isn't great it's really the
scope piece of something yeah I know
it's not us
reven no this casual there's not gonna
be too much Twitter activity because I'm
going to New York for the weekends
and I am the company a social media
manager hey I know social media managers
going on vacation
it sure is a little dim seems damn
picture
at least the contrast is going
Wow why could break so hard left turn
what are you driving which I have around
or just casually the email coach two
truck sisters
um because getting to level 4 on the
highway is much easier than getting to
level 4 in cities also your cost per
unit for trucks can be significantly
higher than for cars in order to have a
viable product
this is Davis playlist this is a Spotify
playlist skull throwback to the 90s
my knees work great time someone killed
their great panda Wow
yeah um I tore it apart
they're quiet - it's casual and we're am
reminding it's minding me of that uh
like don't weird
yeah that was cat and it's just life
people just how open fire can Fitness is
like
do we have any opinion on uber
I'll just say the safety driver should
have been paying attention and attention
should be more enforced once you get
systems that go like ours without
disengagement so I let you guys know it
has the six minute timeout and you know
it's to remind you that you need to
still be in the loop with this car drive
we can help my eyes are straight ahead
on the road and I could react any
scenario that might arise associate is
very important to pay attention while
you're using these systems no matter
what the system is there's no such thing
as a level four self-driving car every
self-driving car today is level two and
requires a human monitor at all times
maybe way most moved a little bit beyond
that but over certainly hasn't you know
I think that the right approach to
solving this problem is kind of the
supercruise style approach so if you
supercruise it has a camera that watches
the driver and make sure that you're
attempting it's the only way to scale
once you get systems
our six minute thing is fine because
that's about how often all compiled it
already messes up if you played a video
game and you had to react to something
that messes up if it messes up once
every minute you'll have no problem if
it messes up once every 10 minutes
you'll probably have no problem and if
it messes up once every you know hour or
two
just watch the driver each other bacon
juice
no it does not change things
automatically
is it true that the Oakley's Classen
calibrating the background
isn't here's a manual they change I can
let it go
dark the street I know yeah why it's so
dark
third price like a dark stormy
we are poor yes we are you don't need
HDR that way oh that's a nice Drive in
Portland in two weeks and the entire
do you have this 360-degree camera
system of your app or what do you think
about Tesla Nevada pilot I heard good
thanks hey I think they're finally using
their data from the people see that
looks so much better yeah well right
like it has to do with the whole balance
in the scene exposure is really our
problem
sorry Skokie so like it's so much better
with the stabilizer I know sorry
anything here with the pedal well we
were going to drive the Acura which has
an installed common pedal the battery is
dead so we took the rabbit stuff
I think the commissary will I thought
replace the lower level
right into designing a company I have
rights of you blown away by the mapping
periscope you guys are killin it
check out our grip pen Oh guys this is
unofficial news I have to loud on
periscope I'm not loaded Paul even
though I am word unofficial news but
grey pandas are coming back in stock to
that today
well you saw a boy they're dropping off
the great bear big news right
damn people are wondering what was the
point of yesterday what was the point of
yesterday we're gonna race this weekend
yeah and we want to make sure all our
stuff for the race is good every one of
the tests don't test racing on public
roads you test racing when close to
course this is insane is what we did how
do you handle reaction as far as a
how do I have the luck reaction just
have reaction let us know you can that
you can react at any time you can take
over at any time you saw me I just
touched you all right Bob well George is
the social media manager for karma and
no one else has access to the Twitter
periscope so the race will be hard to
periscope dan this isn't air what
yeah you guys find any experts and you
can exist
don't you shout
you guys should scope the races yeah
[Music]
you guys gotta keep me in town guys a
future world leader loves thing kazuya's
Wow George you taught leader I'm a
future world troll I am here to troll
I'm your troll and cause trouble for
everybody who takes the world too
seriously that's a that's my goal in
life
charges - no actually yeah hold on the
wheel Jeep Chrysler has UConnect hundred
five scho fees this is more than normal
hey I think Opie's are really better oh
yeah and how do you differentiate
between a no pilot failure causing
engagement and me just disengaging at
light pour your shell rule is all
Jeffrey James and there's a ticket I'm
not gonna engage over by the airport
[Music]
there's one at the part or doesn't want
to arrive once it's the part in a job
well compiled oh yeah yeah people really
like the Mexico yeah yeah so this cars
make maps right now I've owned with the
great bandoneon is out there making maps
great bandoneon NHD are is a mapper
that's amazing what we got here
bigger than a self-driving car it's also
where is the most stealth self-driving
cars like we used to grow up to the
airport with like a lie down on the roof
I was kind of like sketchy
yeah blow when is HDI of R+ coming
everything badly Scopus yeah everybody's
guys dogs see